In international order, please.
Welcome once again to the Natatorium at the Nanjing Olympic Sports Centre.
We could be seeing double here in the final of the women's three-meter springboard competition.
Wu Shengping is on course for the second gold of the Youth Olympic Games.
If she can add the three-meter crowd to her 10-meter title, she will emulate the achievements of Lin You-al four years ago in Singapore, who also landed a golden double.
Again, a good crowd here.
They've supported this event right from the first competition in China, with such a great tradition in diving of course.
And they're enjoying great success as well, so no wonder the numbers have turned out.
That's the schedule, it's the women's three metre springboard final.
Our third final so far in this competition.
Twelve contestants will go.
well there's every chance we could see a repeat of the platform one two three here on the three meter springboard it's the final and divers from ukraine to usa will certainly have other ideas than another chinese victory a good crowd in once again
A reminder of the position after the preliminary competition where we watched nine rounds of diving.
The first five rounds were limited to a total degree of difficulty of 9.5 and those marks are carried forward into this final.
Here is the dive order which doesn't reflect those points that are carried over, rather the scoring from the whole overall competition.
Wu Shengping, the one to beat Orozco Lofa and Lo, also were medalists at 10 meters.
Nine rounds in the preliminary competition, so a demanding schedule for these girls.
Just four rounds for them to go through.
Again, no limit on these darts.
We've got the NBA player there, Yao Ming, distinctive figure in China, of course.
Boy, he'd make a splash.
Well, the gap between the
Preliminary and the final is a big test of Hannah Hagley.
There's Wu Jinping, immersed in her messages.
Oh well, she looks confident.
She should be.
Just waiting for the signal for competition to start.
First up is Sara Carolina Perez Beltran of Colombia.
Just going through those movements.
good atmosphere here in the arena such a great facility really fine setting for this competition it's a big spotlight for these young teenagers
So, the first round, 4-2-1, Salsa.
Crowd not settled down, let's hope the divers can.
2.4 tariff here.
Three more rounds after this, that's a good entry.
Three sevens, decent start.
young Molly Carlson, 15 years of age.
Very tidy.
She has been the Pan American Junior Champion in 2013.
This has been a big test for her though.
59.40, that's a decent start.
Viviane Bach from Switzerland.
Very nice.
Divers hitting a bit of form in this final.
Not a bad entry.
Judges not giving their marks away.
3-6.5s.
From Sweden, Johan Cullindahl.
18 years of age.
Oh dear.
Little bit untidy.
Judge is not too harsh on her.
54 points.
Ingrid de Oliveira opening with a 3.0.
She's got quite a big program of dives ahead of her.
She won bronze at the qualifying event.
Very nice, piped position.
And 63 points.
Gana Kresnoshlike.
Now she's changed this dive from the pike to tuck, which is a lesser degree of difficulty.
Didn't go too well for her in the preliminary of this dive.
Let's see what she can do now.
World Divers have now after the preliminary competition to change a dive and this could have been a good decision.
She's in contention for a medal if she gets into some good form and that's a very good decision three eights
Laura Bilotta in a couple of good free dives in the preliminary competition and a couple of disappointing ones.
Committed totally to that.
Plenty of height off the board.
Just a little bit untidy around the edges, especially that entry.
47.60.
In the two and a half somersault tucked.
Completed this dive quite tidily in preliminary competition.
Well, she had two decent dives, and two rather poor ones.
Needs to find consistency, and she could challenge for a medal.
Six, seven, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, seven and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six
Josephine Schneider.
Inward two and a half somersault tucked.
Just falling away while they're on entry.
Three sevens, fifty six, seventy.
Now, Nozai with a real chance of
repeating her silver from 10 metres here at 3 metres.
Needs to be consistent right the way through.
That's her biggest tariff dive.
And a decent effort, 67.50.
Olofka Lothar will beat forward three and a half somersault.
Just a bit untidy around the edges.
Now here comes the start.
Listen to the applause.
Going for that second gold medal.
Another really good start.
She doesn't have the highest tariff of a schedule, but she's so, so consistently clean.
64.80.
And Wu consolidating her position at the top of the leaderboard.
Luo and Krasnoshnik do very well.
Round 2 Here is Beltran
Inward two and a half somersault tucked.
15-year-old Molly Carson, ranked 7, which would be an encouragement for her.
The crowd are getting behind her, trying to encourage her all the way.
Good height.
Entry could have been smoother, but that's one of her better efforts.
Well done.
Viviane Balt of Switzerland.
It's a very steady dive.
Three seven and a halves.
Veronica Lindahl of Sweden now.
Forward two and a half somersault, one twist.
Just a little bit on the untidy side.
She really commits to her dives though.
Powerful figure.
It really does need to tidy up the details though.
She'll be rather disappointed with three 4.5s.
So Ingrid de Oliveira picks up her score, 37.20 for that forward three and a half somersault.
and we now move on to Ukraine's Kresna Shilik and she will be attempting a forward two and a half somersault 2.4 degree of difficulty there's the ukraine coach looking a little bit anxiously i have to say but she has performed well throughout the competition so far nice entry super entry there for gana for ukraine and that
105 B dive Gives us the forward two and a half somersault.
That's the code Good height and you can hear probably the scores in the background eights and sevens good entry should be happy with that
57.60 then for the Ukrainian girl.
She's in contention as we move now to Italy's Laura Bilotta.
Bilotta with a forward two and a half somersault with one twist.
Lots of pikes involved in this.
I'm a little bit overcooked on the entry but a good effort from Bellotta.
See what the judges think about that but she gets good height.
Most of the rotation done before she comes past the board and enters the water just a little bit untidily.
You can hear reflected in the scores there Six and a half sixes there and the six and a half fifty five point five then she's ranked three total of 301 Good scores for Laura Bellotta of Italy We're in now with Grosia Leydon Mahoney of the USA She'll be going backwards two and a half somersault with tucks and
yeah good rotations in fact over the top of the board and then the moment she came underneath it was a little bit fast in fact over rotation when she didn't need it she needed to open up a fraction earlier you can see that extra bit of splash
Pressure laden Mahoney then, 54.6.
Getting up into second position.
So doing really well here for the second round.
Here's Schneider of Germany.
2.8 degree of difficulty and that means it's a back two and a half somersault.
Again in the tuck position.
So same dive as we've just witnessed.
See whether or not she can open a bit earlier.
Good concentration, and a similar kind of problem on that entry.
Mild applause from this natatorium here at the Olympic Sports Centre.
Good, close position in the air, very tidy in the air, but just that entry, a little bit overcooked there, you can see, a little bit of extra splash, and the judges respond with scores
There you go, 46.2, back in seventh rank, 294.80 then for Schneider.
Now this is very interesting, the Malaysian girl Sia Yi, Lo Sia Yi has been superb throughout the competition here.
107C, that means a four with three and a half somersault with tucks, here we go.
Lovely, just maybe a little under the vertical for the entry, but they really like the look of this girl.
She's been working so well.
The Malaysian diving has come of age.
For the last decade or so, a little bit off to the side there at the entry, but she really has put together a very, very impressive performance.
There you go, 335.70, rank one at the moment, 54.6 for that one, slightly disappointing.
Mexico now with Alejandra Orozco Loza.
She's got a back two and a half somersault.
Needs that real height off the ball which it gets well and again just a little bit of extra splash but that's got the approval of the coach which is the most important thing.
again nice height and then just a little bit of extra movement in the air which she didn't quite need just have a look at the opening up with the hips going forward yeah and there was trying to adjust in the air it's an extraordinary ability these divers have adjusting the air for the entry 54 60 that puts her in bronze medal position at the moment 3 15 and now well
There's something special there is always in competitions and here we see it once again Wu Shengpeng she's going to do a backward two and a half somersault 18 years old and I tell you she is quite phenomenal she knows where she is exactly in the air all the time despite the speed of rotation watch out
and again good entry I don't know whether you noticed but there was that moment where she's visualizing the dive her eyes are closed and just before she goes for it and that is the moment where she says feels wow this is the moment we're going to open up get the entry and just listen to the scores come through that's a strong strong dive
She will take over the lead right here, no doubt at all.
There you go, rank one.
2.8 difficulty, 8s and 8.5, 68.60.
Wu Shengping does what is expected of her.
There she is at the top of the table.
Malaysia's Luo Xiaoyi in second, and Krasnolzlic from Ukraine is in third position overall at the moment.
The atmosphere around the Nanjing Natatorium is really, really exciting.
They know they've got a home crowd favorite here.
There's nothing that brings an atmosphere to life like a very, very popular and very impressive home favorite.
But here's Sarah Carolina Perez Beltrán preparing the board again for her new dive.
That'll be a back two and a half somersault.
In terms of the performances before, we had the German girl actually coming up four places from that last dive.
Schneider, Josephine Schneider, so a really good performance.
56.7 for a first dive, 46 for a second, and then the third one, 71.65.
Very impressive.
Here we go, third dive.
That was just under rotated there were very very unlucky for Beltran So the back two and a half somersault just have a look at it She goes too early with the open up and there she just doesn't make it off to the side a little bit as well Unfortunate look good from the start and now it's going to be under four under five something Listen to the scores of this and
32.20, 315 altogether.
It was too tough a dive for her to execute.
And here's the youngster Molly Carlson, very young.
I think she's just 15, if I'm not mistaken.
And certainly enjoying her first out experience here for Canada.
Third place back with two and a half somersaults.
Big concentration again, going through the motions before she actually executes the dive.
Now just a little bit overdone.
Oh, it's so close to being a very good dive, but she will definitely be marked down for that entry.
You can see that extra splash.
This is what the Chinese girls don't do.
They really know where they are in the air and their timing of opening is perfect.
36.40 then.
Four fives and a four.
So Vivian Bath now from Switzerland.
She gets a really good cheer.
There's a lot of Swiss supporters inside this natatorium.
Can she keep her concentration back with two and a half somersaults?
Again, a 2.8 difficulty.
It's the toughest she takes on.
Entry is everything.
father is a coach and the game doesn't quite make it he's happy though and as long as dad is happy I guess you can say that you've given it your best
You can tell that extra splash is so, so important.
You enter like a knife coming into the water.
You can't create so much and expect to have top scores.
4-5, 4-5, 4-0, 36.4.
She's got a good total though, 335.
Here's Lindahl of Sweden.
Veronica Lindahl, this will be also back two and a half somersault, same degree of difficulty.
She's 11th overall before this dive.
And another one that just didn't quite execute at the end.
Everything that happens above the board there is good, looks solid, and then the opening and the delivery not quite there.
Should be marked down once again.
It just looks so good until that moment.
It's overcooked on rotation.
Here's the scores coming up, 35 together, 320 in total.
And again, four fives and fours.
It's not good enough if you want to get up into the medals.
Here's Brazil, under 300 in total at the moment.
Big, big dive required here.
It's a degree of difficulty of three.
Forward two and a half somersaults.
One twist.
This is huge.
So difficult.
Good girl.
Oh, yes.
Ingrid de Oliveira came up with certainly the best dive of this round so far.
Watch this.
Great height.
Beautiful movement in the air.
And then the open up.
She saw the water early and look at the finish.
Very nice.
We've got sevens and a six-five, so that'll score well.
Here's the confirmation of the score right now.
Good girl.
63 points.
362.357s.
All around, they must be very happy with that for Brazil.
Gana Prash-Noshilic.
She is trying now forward two and a half somersaults, again with pikes.
So hip extension, very, very important here.
In third place at the moment, can she improve on that position?
She's been through it twice now.
Can she deliver?
It's a great dive.
Oh yes.
The back two and a half somersault, 2.8 degree of typical deep.
She'll certainly stand a chance here of holding the bronze if not improving.
Just fractionally under, but it was well disguised.
Sixes and sevens here.
Just a little under the Brazilian score, but that 391.90 takes the first position at the moment.
57.4 for the dive itself.
So excellent work from Resh Noshalik.
So Laura Bellotta.
She is in seventh place before this dive.
55.5 she had for the last one.
That was a forward two and a half.
Now we've got reverse.
Watch the reverse movement here for 2.8.
There you go.
Oh and a good ever accept right at the end.
Those heels just came over a fraction.
Didn't cut through the water as she would have liked, but it's a good aerial movement.
Landing just a little bit extra.
You'll see.
Again, it's got a good degree of difficulty, so 53.2 takes it up into bronze at the moment, although we know we've got some high quality divers still to come.
Grecia Leighton Mahoney, coming from Massachusetts in the United States.
And I'm sure they'll all be watching her, all her friends, her pals, all her relatives.
It's a most wonderful opportunity for these young people to show how dedicated they are to their sport.
It's a reverse two and a half somersault.
Nicely done.
Oh, much better than last time.
The back two and a half didn't work.
The reverse two and a half certainly did.
That was very good indeed.
Just look at it again.
The control above the board.
The opening out.
Very nice entry too.
Look at that.
Hardly a splash.
So, yeah, seven.
Fifth at the moment.
Will this improve her position?
63 dead takes her up into seventh overalls 375 points point eight zero So that's a really good.
Dye that would have done a no harm at all the American girl Graciel aid Mahoney.
We now move forward to Germany and the Josephine Schneider from Dresden She was
involved in the 12th Youth World Championships 2012, a couple of years ago.
And now, and again, just overplayed her hand on the rotation.
But it was a good attempt there by Schneider.
Reverse two and a half somersaults.
She improved last time.
I'm not sure that the entry will do her any favors.
She was just a little bit off the vertical here.
Yeah, so it will be marked down for that entry as well, I think.
But there you go, 45 altogether.
Ranked sixth, 339.8, just as expected.
So the Malaysian girl, she's called Joey.
Lo Jah Yee.
From Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, they have made great strides in their diving, of course.
We know their success has bred success and they've got a whole string of good divers coming through very strongly.
Certainly favorites for the Southeast Asian Games next year.
Maybe we'll be contesting the Asian Games in a while as well.
Here we go, back two and a half somersaults.
Land it!
Oh yes!
Good girl!
Well, Southeast Asia can be proud of that one.
That back two-and-a-half somersault entry was absolutely super.
Look at that.
Hardly a smidgen of a splash.
Good work.
And just listen to the score.
Sevens, eights, seven and a half, eights.
It will be big.
Look at that.
Sixty-three.
And Luo Xiaoyi takes the 398.70.
Look at the coach loving it.
You have to say, well done.
Brilliant.
Coach is Wang Qiang.
Aleksandr Alekhandarov is up now.
She comes from Jelisco.
And this one is an inward two and a half somersault.
Again, it's all about the timing of the entry.
And again she just overplays her hand a little bit.
So tough and it's so easy for me to sit here and suggest that she could have done a lot better.
I'm sure she would think that she could have done better herself but everything was good until the entry.
You can understand how the judges are looking at this, can't you?
Look at that, 36.40.
Back in rank six position overall, four and a halfs.
We knew it was going to be that.
Now, can this young lady get up into the eights and nines right here?
She is from Nanjing, Wu Shengping.
It's no wonder that she's bringing the crowds in.
It's fantastic.
She's from Huan Wu High School and Hu Jie is her coach.
Let's have a look at this.
Reverse two and a half somersaults.
What do you think?
You reckon that this is popular around here?
You betcha.
Just look at it.
it was the wide tucks to start and then she closes up and it's a look at that closes up for the entry it's beautiful
just have a listen and look at this response from the judges 64.4 sevens and one eighth there in fact there's several eights they were discounted of course the degree of dignity but that after three rounds here is the score Wu Shengping the local girl 4.30 she's definitely going to be uncatchable here 4.30.85
Low, Jiayi, the Malaysian, in second place and continuing in third place overall is the Ukrainian girl, Kresna Shilik.
So this is now the all-important fourth round, the one that decides the medals.
And you have to say that every single one of these girls has not only had a fabulous introduction to big-time competition,
but they have contributed enormously to the success of the Youth Olympic Games.
It's been stunning watching them perform but also interacting as well.
The atmosphere is fabulous.
Here's now Sarah Caroline Perez Beltran.
She comes from Colombia and the coach is Juan Camposano.
The reverse two and a half somersaults.
It doesn't quite stick on entry.
the tucks there just a little wayward but again she would have learned so much from this experience they've now got some real footage to work on a little bit off the side you see the vertical position was not held came a little bit to the side and that was the result lots of water
So here's the score, 30.80, 345.8 at the overall position.
Molly Carlson invited here from Thunder Bay in Canada and certainly a lot of people will be looking to her for the future.
She is a young girl.
had fair good experiences at the Pan-Americans last year.
Gold there.
So she has got huge potential and again just a little bit undercooked it but that reversed two and a half somersault.
It certainly will be scoring reasonably well.
There was no disaster there.
That was the one.
She just opened a little bit late
And then kept on rotating in the vertical position, which is not a good idea when you're diving.
Let's have a look at her scores then, coming up shortly.
There she is, but she's had a wonderful experience.
43.40 then, 388 in total.
Jumps to the top of the tree for the moment, just after two competitors.
So Vivian Bath right now.
Yeah, they know.
In Switzerland they call her Bibi.
Vivi, there's a bit of life in that, there's no question about that.
Yep, and her father is her coach.
So the back, one and a half somersaults, one and a half twists.
Nice, oh yes, very good, it's a 2.4 degree of difficulty, he likes it.
Yeah, a lot of these parent coaches obviously living their own dreams through their offspring.
But I tell you right there, that's the best spring right there.
It's back one and a half somersaults, one and a half twists.
Very nice entry.
A little bit low on the degree of difficulty, but the execution will definitely score well.
Let's have a listen.
There you go, in the sevens it was very, very good.
Let's have the graphic now, 48.
and 383.70 he's a happy chappie you can tell so Swedish girl Veronica Lindahl she's back again still in 11th place so anything that will bring her up the ladder into the 10th position and beyond will be great
Oh yeah well almost complete it was just not quite there a little bit too much rotation that forward three and a half somersault that's what we've got to emphasize three and a half times she's in the air we're on the springboard here this is not the 10 meter you've got to get huge height to accomplish that 2.8 degree of difficulty almost got the entry
Great there.
Vertical position but there we go.
Sixes and sevens there.
Discounted.
Couple of them.
Almost got it.
Really perfect.
Let's have a look.
53.20 in total then.
Sixes and one seven there.
So, Brazil.
Here's Ingrid de Oliveira.
Back two and a half somersaults.
This is a difficult dive.
Difficulty 3.0.
The same as her third dive.
Difficulty.
What's the bouncing?
She didn't quite make it, did she?
She didn't quite make those pikes.
It's much easier, obviously, when you get into tucks.
Once you've got those long levers, really, really needing to rotate, it's so tough.
Didn't quite get it over the top, did she?
And failed with the vertical entry.
You could tell why she was jumping on the board to start with, though.
She needed absolutely everything in height in order to accomplish it.
Difficult dive should be marked down for the entry, but yeah 30 altogether threes and 3.5.
That's tough But you gamble you take the risk if it doesn't come off, it's tough right is gonna cross nosh Shalik
Apologies for having trouble with her name before.
She's from the National University of Physical Training.
And Ukraine can be proud of this young girl.
I tell you, she's really, really impressive.
Oh, lovely.
Reverse two and a half somersaults.
2.8 degree of difficulty, and I tell you what, the Ukrainian coaches do not wear their hearts on their sleeves very often.
He must be absolutely delighted.
As far as he's concerned, that is perfection.
Good girl.
That is excellent.
Third place, she might even push the Malaysian girl.
Xia Yi, Luo Xia Yi, would have looked at that and thought, oh my goodness, I really have got to pull out the stops.
Great.
That could be the bronze medal dive.
Let's have a listen to it.
67.2.
Good girl.
459.10.
Absolutely stunning.
Well done.
Laura Bellotta, known as Lala.
And of course, we've got the mascots here, known as Lele.
So Lala will get a Lele if she gets any further down the line here.
First in the European Junior Championships in 2013.
So Laura Bellotta of Italy, backward two and a half somersaults, 2.8 degree of difficulty.
And another good attempt there.
That 2.8.
See the big difference between that and de Oliveira was that she was doing tucks with her somersaults as opposed to pikes.
It makes it a little bit easier and of course she could get right over into the entry position very much easier.
Good girl.
Laura Bellotta.
Six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half, six and a half
You've probably heard the scores there, six and a halves.
And six is 54.6.
Up into second position overall at the moment, 409 points.
Coach looks smugly impressed by that.
Okay, Gracia Leydon Mahoney from the United States is up next.
Also likes gymnastics, ice hockey, you can tell, and lacrosse and ballet and soccer.
My goodness me, the all-round athlete, Gracia Leydon Mahoney, USA.
Reverse one and a half somersaults, two and a half twists, 2.9 degree of difficulty.
It's all action here.
Yeah, I think she'll be pretty pleased with that.
We are in the women's three-meter springboard final.
And you have to say, we've done the halfway in the final round and it's all now boiling up to really, really impressive finish here.
Good girl, she really completed the twists and the somersaults very, very well.
It's a good score.
all together with the DD with a degree of difficulty it's 53.65 for 29.45 and a high five there from the coach right Josephine Schneider let's see whether or not she can improve she dropped back a little bit there back in ninth at the moment forward two and a half somersaults one twist
Oh well, didn't quite make the entry but all the elements were there for the dive so it will be pretty well judged but again it is that absolutely all-important entry that makes such a difference and she was underneath it wasn't she?
Didn't quite have the speed for the entry.
I was going to say if she gets five she'll be lucky but they are undefined.
There you go 40.5 and 380 takes her into seventh place ranked at the moment and now this is an all-important one currently second position Low Chia Yi of Malaysia
and it was a brave brave effort earlier by the Ukrainian girl but here this is an all-important back one and a half somersault one and a half twist 2.4 degree of difficulty not a high degree of difficulty so the execution the entry in the water absolutely vital and a little bit over the top just a smidgen not much but it looks like Ukraine will be celebrating that one I don't know
Nice moment there for Xia Yi.
She says thank you to the judges and to the crowd.
And that Huang Qiang, I'm not sure he'll be happy with this because it was a 2.4 degree of difficulty and the entry just a little bit overcooked with the heels, wasn't it?
You can just feel this, you're a bit anxious.
Let's have a listen to the scores.
Oh, I don't think it's quite good enough.
It's number two.
Yeah, it's number two at the top there.
So 48 altogether.
And I knew there was going to be a little bit of problem there for Loh Zhaoyi.
It is, in fact, the Ukrainian girl who's come up there, Ghana Krasnoshili, who has come up now to a very, very good position where she's still leading with one to go.
Seventh overall at the moment, Alejandro Orozca Losa.
She is the Mexican girl with a forward two and a half somersault, one twist.
And again, just a little bit under the vertical, that will be marked down, but a brave effort because that's a 3.0 degree of difficulty.
Yeah, fabulous finish.
Ah, right.
Okay, this is the one.
It looks very much at the moment.
Lo Zha Yi, the Malaysian, has got into bronze medal position.
Krasno Shilik has come up into silver medal position because there will be no chance, I'm sure, when Wu Shengping comes to the board.
There is the score, 46.50.
She's come up into fifth ranked at the moment, but of course, well, after Wu Shengping,
has performed her dive that'll drop her back into sixth so good work for the Mexican but this is what it's all about the final dive again it's a very easy dive relatively back one and a half somersault one and a half twist the girl from Nanjing will set us alive with a gold medal performance right here final dive three meter springboard for women gold medal dive
Oh my goodness.
You want it simple, you want it beautiful, you want it controlled.
Wu Xiangping is definitely the real deal.
And Zhu Jie will be happy with that.
She showed us applause in that cutaway.
And just look at these replays.
Dream performances all round.
Perfect position in the air.
And look at the entry.
This is how you dive.
The eights and the eights and a half, it just tells the world we've now seen another Olympic, Youth Olympic champion here in Nepal.
61.2, it's been a fantastic performance.
We are going to see a smile in a moment and certainly smiles all around, I'm sure.
Very, very impressive.
the Malaysian coach there will be just celebrating a medal not quite a silver commiserating is the Ukrainian coach as well because he has picked up the silver with his Ghana Krasnoshlyk and there's the final scores Wu Xiangping absolutely
Performed to perfection, 492.05 takes the gold, Gana Krasnozlic takes the silver, and Lo Zayi takes the bronze.
So all the other performances there, Ingrid D'Oliveira came up very nicely as well.
It has been a fabulous contest, there's been loads of really, really high-end performances and of course with these girls being put on the
on the podium in terms of the spotlight it's a really really difficult thing to continue to put on your uh your top performance with the knowing that not just the crowd have the expectations for the people at home because we are going worldwide with our coverage here of the Youth Olympic Games in Nanjing 214.
Lele comes out to greet the crowd again
And in fact, I read that she was designed on the colorful pebbles that are on the shorelines around here.
That shows they like skimming across the water.
Well, there won't be too much skimming at the moment this afternoon with them, but certainly the cameras will be picking them up in just a couple of moments and delighting the children, I'm sure.
It's been a fantastic time for all of us here in Nanjing.
In every sport we've seen fabulous performances but we've also seen some extraordinary camaraderie, some wonderful new relationships developing and of course the ambitions of the IOC to promote peace through unity of the youth of the world is just a marvelous
ambition and certainly we've seen many occasions in which that ambition has been realised.
It's quite stunning.
The second edition of the Youth Olympic Games has been quite remarkable.
A little bit of housekeeping work going on inside the Natatorium here in the Olympic Sports Centre.
Just preparing for the presentation in just a couple of minutes.
It is quite remarkable the way that China's diving expertise has come to the fore.
I well remember back in Barcelona in 92, being on Montjuic and seeing
Fu Min Tian putting up an extraordinary performance into what appeared to be the city's cathedral there, the Sagrada Familia.
It was absolutely amazing.
An iconic photograph, never to be forgotten.
So you're on a mountain, on a hill, watching divers dive into the city centre.
It was just phenomenal.
Since those days, of course, China's gymnastics has come to the heady heights of golds all around.
Since Li Ning's era, of course.
And now everyone measures and gives the benchmark to China for creating the special, special performers.
Well certainly that reputation has been enhanced here at these Youth Olympic Games.
We've seen something very special from Wu Shengping.
Quite remarkable.
so
Ladies and gentlemen, please raise your hands and shake the board together.
if if
Thank you.
So we'll be getting the women's three meter springboard victory ceremony in just a couple of moments and I hope if you are watching that little montage of Wu Xiangpeng certainly in the slow-mo.
the ultracam kind of vision that you can just appreciate how fantastic how wonderfully disciplined coordinated beautifully trained not only she is but others as well but she is absolutely the cream of the crop very impressive
Ladies and gentlemen, the victory ceremony for the Women's Women's Springboard.
Ladies and gentlemen, the second season of the Summer Youth Olympic Games, the three-point jump and the award ceremony will now begin.
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome to the stage,
So the women's three meter springboard final victory ceremony is just about to get underway.
And there, the cameras, the eyes, everyone is looking at this young lady, Wu Shengping.
The girl from Nanjing who has not only done well, she has become champion of the Youth Olympic Games three meter springboard with excellent performances.
No one could match her in terms of her scores.
She was sensational.
Introduction of the VIPs who will make the presentations, but it's a huge moment here.
Gunilla Lindbergh, IOC executive board member.
A great privilege for her to be here in the Natatorium inside the Olympic Sports Centre.
And so the first of the presentations we'll be having
Lu Jia Yi of Malaysia.
There she is on the right of screen.
Joey, she's known as a great performance.
Just couldn't quite deliver the final dive and she knows that she should have had a silver, but a great performance nevertheless.
Here's the bronze medal.
to go with another silver medal from the 10-meter.
So a really great performance.
Lala, she gets us a souvenir as well.
But a fabulous performance for Malaysia.
The NOC there will be delighted with this bronze medal for Loh Chia Yeh.
So we have Loh Chia Yeh.
Silver medalist, representing the ring.
The winner of the silver medal is Loh Chia Yeh.
Well, what a fabulous third dive she had.
The entry you could tell was going to be delighting everybody.
The coach was delighted with it.
He was almost ecstatic with praise and it proved to be the difference between bronze and silver for Ghana.
And I tell you, she will
Be dreaming about that for many, many months, if not years, if not a lifetime to come.
It was extraordinary.
Great work by the Ukrainian champion.
459.1 was Ghana's score.
But 492.05 was the score of this young lady.
Wu Xiangpeng, the girl from Nanjing.
How popular is this?
from the Nanjing Xuanwu High School, just around the corner.
She comes through the natatorium here and takes a gold medal.
And everyone here was oohing and eyeing.
How did she manage to be so perfect?
Fantastic.
China, gold medal, Wu Xiangping, again victorious.
And now the national anthem for the People's Republic of China.
What an extraordinary achievement.
She started competing 2006, eight years ago.
Her hero is Chun Ruolin and she wants to be world champion.
Can you believe that she won't achieve that?
Amazing performance.
Gold medal, Wu Xunpeng, Silver to Ghana, Krasnoshlyk and Luo Xiaoyi is the bronze medal winner in the three meter diving for women.
Ladies and gentlemen, the winner of this year's Chinese Games is the winner of this year's Chinese Games.
Let's give her another round of applause.
Thank you for watching!
Boys and girls, ladies and gentlemen, we hope you have enjoyed today's competition.
Please follow our instructions on the way down.
Please make sure to leave a thumbs up if you see anyone in front of you.
Thank you for your cooperation.